Awesome night. Epic aftermath.
Walk of Shame is a comedy film directed by Steven Brill.
A reporter's dream of becoming a news anchor is compromised after a
one-night stand leaves her stranded in downtown L.A.
without a phone, car, ID or money - and only 8 hours to make it
to the most important job interview of her life.
Meghan, played by Elizabeth Banks.
Gordon, played by James Marsden.
Rose, played by Gillian Jacobs.
Denise, played by Sarah Wright.
Officer Dave, played by Ethan Suplee.
Officer Walter, played by Bill Burr.
Walk of Shame is a 2014 American comedy film written and directed by Steven Brill and
starring Elizabeth Banks, James Marsden, Gillian Jacobs, and Sarah Wright Olsen.
The film was released in select theaters and through video on demand
in the United States on May 2, 2014, by Focus World.
Walk of Shame garnered negative reviews from critics who commended Banks' performance but criticized Brill's filmmaking
for creating an unspectacular comedic romp filled with broad caricatures and misogynistic views on women.
The film grossed $8.1 million worldwide against a
production budget of $15 million.
The film explores themes of journalist, one-night stand, blonde, newswoman.
The tone is lighthearted.